--- Real News 1 ---
 Kerry to go to Paris in gesture of sympathy U.S. Secretary of State John F. Kerry said Monday that he will stop in Paris later this week, amid criticism that no top American officials attended Sunday�s unity march against terrorism.

Kerry said he expects to arrive in Paris Thursday evening, as he heads home after a week abroad. He said he will fly to France at the conclusion of a series of meetings scheduled for Thursday in Sofia, Bulgaria. He plans to meet the next day with Foreign Minister Laurent Fabius and President Francois Hollande, then return to Washington.

The visit by Kerry, who has family and childhood ties to the country and speaks fluent French, could address some of the criticism that the United States snubbed France in its darkest hour in many years.

The French press on M 

--- Real News 2 ---
 The Battle of New York: Why This Primary Matters It's primary day in New York and front-runners Hillary Clinton and Donald Trump are leading in the polls.

Trump is now vowing to win enough delegates to clinch the Republican nomination and prevent a contested convention. But Sens.Ted Cruz, R-Texas, Bernie Sanders, D-Vt., and Ohio Gov. John Kasich and aren't giving up just yet.

A big win in New York could tip the scales for both the Republican and Democratic front-runners in this year's race for the White House. Clinton and Trump have each suffered losses in recent contests, shifting the momentum to their rivals.

"We have won eight out of the last nine caucuses and primaries! Cheer!" Sanders recently told supporters.

While wins in New York for Trump and Clinton are expected, the margins 
